I'm sorry that y'all saw Jamal Bowman pull the fire alarm, which people are like up in arms about,
which is hilarious to me because the same people up in arms are the people who are trying to shut
the government down. However, those same people tried to slide the Democrats a bill and not give
them any time to read the bill. They've only had five minutes to read the bill. They could slide
anything in that bill. And then if it passes, now the Democrats are blamed for letting a bill pass
that the Republicans put a whole bunch of funny shit in. So Jamal Bowman being a real one,
and if they say, nah, we need more time. They're going to be like, ah, there was only five minutes.
Now you're the one shutting the government down. He could have had a staffer do that. And he said,
I'm going to do it. I'm going to do it myself. And those of y'all who don't get it, you cannot win
playing fair with cheaters. That's why they go low. We go high. Don't work.
So you better hope that the people that are fighting for you are willing to go where they
need to go because them other folks are in the gutter and we cannot go down there with them.
But we need folks who are willing to step down there to pull shit back up. Salute.